Guide to the James Perkins papers,1963-1969.
Perkins, James papers,1963-1969.
- Series IV. 1963-1969
  - Annual Report, Cornell Program in Social Psychology., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 70)
  - Annual Report, New York State Veterinary College., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 71)
  - Summary, Cornell University Committee on Conferences., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 72)
  - Annual Report, Assistant to the President for Development and University Relations., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 73)
  - Annual Report, University Relations Office., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 74)
  - Annual Report, Development Office., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 75)
  - Annual Report, Alumni Office., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 76)
  - Annual Report, News Bureau., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 77)
  - Annual Report, Medical College., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 78)
  - Annual Report, Vice President for Business., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 79)
  - Annual Report, Office of the Director of the Budget., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 80)
  - Annual Report, Office of the Treasurer., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 81)
  - Annual Report, Office of the Controller., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 82)
  - Annual Report, Office of the University Counsel., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 83)
  - Annual Report of the Secretary of the Corporation., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 84)
  - Annual Report of the Dean of the School of Nursing., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 85)
  - Annual Report, University Placement Office., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 86)
  - Annual Report, Vice President of the Business Depts., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 87)
  - Annual Report, School of Hotel Administration., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 88)
  - Annual Report, Associate Dean of Students., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 89)
  - Annual Report, University Libraries., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 90)
  - Annual Report, Committee on Conferences., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 91)
  - Annual Report, New York State College of Home Economics., 1962-65 (Box 40, Folder 92)
  - Annual Report, School of Education., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 93)
  - Annual Report, Cornell Social Science Research Center., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report, Center for International Studies., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Annual Statistics, Registrars Office., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, Office of the Dean of Students., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, New York State College of Agriculture., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, Director of the Division of Summer Session and Extramural Courses., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report Law School., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report, Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report, School of Education., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report, College of Architecture., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report, Associate Dean of Students., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report, College of Arts and Sciences., 1963-65 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report, Office of the Director of the Budget., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report, office of the Treasurer., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Annual Report, Office of the Controller., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Annual Report, Dean of the University Faculty., 1963-64 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Annual Report, Educational Placement Bureau., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report, Medical College., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Annual Report, Vice President for Research and Advanced Studies., 1963-65 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report, University Health Services., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report, Dean of Students -Counseling., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report, University Relations, Development, Alumni Relations, and University Publications., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Annual Report, Graduate School of Nutrition., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Annual Report, Military Science Dept., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Naval Science., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Annual Report, New York State Veterinary College., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Annual Report, Dean of the University Faculty., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Annual Report, University News Bureau., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Annual Report, University Testing and 1 Service Bureau., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Year-End Review, WHCU., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Annual Report, Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Annual Report, Alumni Office., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Annual Report, College of Engineering., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Annual Report, School of Hotel I Administration., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Annual Report, Office of the Secretary of the University., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Annual Report, Registrar., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Air Science., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Annual Report, Willard Straight Hall., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Annual Report, New York State College of Home Economics., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Annual Report, Medical College., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Annual Report, University Health Services., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Annual Report, Cornell Social Science Research Center., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Annual Report, Dean of Admissions and Financial Aid., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Annual Report, CURW., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Annual Report, Veterinary Virus Research Institute., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Annual Report, Center for International Studies., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - President's Reports Check-off Lists., 1957-63 (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Annual Report, Dean of the College of Arts and Sciences., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Annual Report, New York State Veterinary College., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - Annual Report, Graduate School of Nutrition., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - Annual Report, Cornell University - New York Hospital School of Nursing., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Naval Science., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Annual Report, Graduate School., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - Annual Report, School of Education., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - Annual Report, University Libraries., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - Annual Report, Director of the Division of Summer Session and Extramural Courses., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - Annual Report, Military Science Dept., 1962-62 (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - Annual Report, Physical Education and Athletics., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 58)
  - Annual Report, Placement Service., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - Annual Report, University Relations, Development, Alumni Affairs., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 60)
  - Annual Report, Division of Unclassified Students., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 61)
  - Annual Report, New York state School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 62)
  - Annual Report, New York State College of Agriculture., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 63)
  - Annual Report, College of Architecture., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 64)
  - Annual Report, University Publisher., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 65)
  - Annual Report, University Faculty., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 66)
  - Annual Report, Vice President of Business Depts., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 67)
  - Annual Report, Vice President for Research and Advanced Studies., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 68)
  - Annual Report, Cornell University - New York Hospital School of Nursing., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 69)
  - Annual Report, Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 70)
  - Annual Report, School of Hotel Administration., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 71)
  - Annual Report, New York State College of Home Economics., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 72)
  - Annual Report, Dean of Admissions., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 73)
  - Biennial Report, Andrew Dickson White Museum of Art., 1964-66 (Box 41, Folder 74)
  - Annual Report, Military Science Dept., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 75)
  - Annual Report, Director of the Budget., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 76)
  - Annual Report, Director of the Division of Summer Session and Extramural Courses., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 77)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Naval Science., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 78)
  - Annual Report, Office of the University Proctor., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 79)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of the Air Force., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 80)
  - Annual Report, School of Education., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 81)
  - Annual Report, Center for International Studies., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 82)
  - Annual Report, college of Arts and Sciences., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 83)
  - Annual Report, New York State Veterinary College., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 84)
  - Annual Report, Medical College., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 85)
  - Annual Report, College of Engineering., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 86)
  - Annual Report, Military Science Dept., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 87)
  - Annual Report, New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 88)
  - Annual Report from John L. Munschauer., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 89)
  - Annual Report, New York State College of Agriculture., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 90)
  - Annual Report, Office of the Vice Provost., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 91)
  - Annual Report, Registrar., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 92)
  - Annual Report, Office of Institutional Studies., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 93)
  - Annual Report, Office of Regional Resources and Development., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 94)
  - Annual Report, Cornell Plantations., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 95)
  - Annual Report, University Planning Office., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 96)
  - Annual Report, University Counsel., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 97)
  - Annual Report, Secretary of the Corporation., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 98)
  - Annual Report, Office of the Controller., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 99)
  - Annual Report, University Publications., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 100)
  - Annual Report, Coordinator of Alumni and Development Records., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 101)
  - Annual Report, News Bureau., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 102)
  - Annual Report, Alumni Office., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 103)
  - Annual Report, University Development., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 104)
  - Annual Report, Office of the Treasurer., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 105)
  - Annual Report, University Libraries., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 106)
  - Annual Report, College of Architecture., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 107)
  - Annual Report, Educational Placement Bureau., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 108)
  - Annual Report, Graduate School., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 109)
  - Report on Undergraduate Instruction., 1966 (Box 41, Folder 110)
  - Annual Reports, Morris G. Bishop Correspondence., 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 111)
  - President's Committee to Study the New York State College of Agriculture at Cornell University.
    - Proposal for a Study of the New York State College of Agriculture, and Related Material., 1964-66 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - "The New York State College of Agriculture and the Next Quarter Century"; Report of the President's Committee, etc., 1966 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Report Draft., 1966 (Box 42, Folder 3-6)
    - Letters to David Pimentel., 1965-66 (Box 42, Folder 7-9)
    - Minutes of Committee., 1965-66 (Box 42, Folder 10-15)
    - Miscellaneous Background Material., 1960-66 (Box 42, Folder 16-29)
    - Gould P. Colman Drafts and Notes., 1966 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - SUNY Master Plan., 1964 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - International Agricultural Development Publications., 1960s (Box 42, Folder 32-33)
  - President's Committee on Student Involvement in Decision Making (Morison Commission).
    - Chairman's Report., 1969 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Bibliography, Cost Sheets, Miscellaneous Printed Material., 1968 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, Working Papers, Drafts., 1968 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, Reports, Memoranda., 1968 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Minutes., 1968 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, Memoranda., 1968 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, Reports, Working Papers., 1968 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, Working Papers., 1968 (Box 43, Folder S)
    - Minutes, Working Papers, Reports., 1969 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, Working Papers., 1969 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Minutes, Correspondence, Reports, Working Papers., 1968-69 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Reports, Working Papers, Outlines., 1968 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Reports, Accounts, Receipts., 1968-69 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Accounts, Receipts., 1968-69 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Cornell Work-Scholarship Program., 1968 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Education.
    - Ideas and Proposals., 1967-68 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Reports., 1967-68 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Minutes., 1967-68 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Publicity., 1967-68 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Memoranda, Reports., 1967-68 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Proposals., 1968-69 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Minutes, Proposals, and Correspondence., 1968-69 (Box 43, Folder 22)
      Bolgiano, Ralph; Hughes, Robert E.; Cooke, W.D.
    - Minutes, Correspondence, Proposals., 1968-69 (Box 43, Folder 23)
      Morison, Robert S.; S trout, Gushing.
    - Reports., 1967-68 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Special University Commission of April, 1968 (Williams Commission).
    - I Report of the Commission., 1968 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Transcript of Testimony, 10 April 1968., 1968 (Box 43, Folder 26)
      McPhelin, Michael.
    - Transcript of Testimony, 11 April 1968., 1968 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Transcript of Testimony, 12 April 1968., 1968 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Transcript of Testimony, 15 April 1968., 1968 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Transcript of Testimony, 16 April 1968., 1968 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Transcript of Testimony, 17 April 1968., 1968 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Transcripts and Documents., 1968 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - Report, Working Papers., 1968 (Box 43, Folder 33-35)
    - Tape Recordings 3923-3928 (Box 43)
    - Transcripts 3923-3928 (Box 43)
  - Cornell Latin American Year, Projects and Reports., 1964-65 (Box 43, Folder 36)
    MacLeish, William H.
  - Cornell Latin American Year, Correspondence. MacLeish, William H., 1964-66 (Box 43, Folder 37-38)
  - Tompkins County United Fund., 1968 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Cornell University News Bureau releases., 1964-68 (Box 43, Folder 40-42)
  - Cornell University Centennial Convocation., 1965 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Colleges and Universities Inaugurations., 1963-65 (Box 43, Folder 44-48)
  - Congratulations to Cornell University at the Dedication of Clark Hall from National Academy of Engineering., 1965 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - Annual Report, Graduate School., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report, Graduate School of Nutrition., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, Cornell Law School., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, Aerospace Studies., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, New York State Veterinary College., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, Division of Biological Sciences., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report, Cornell University - New York Hospital School of Nursing., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report, School of Hotel Administration., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder S)
  - Annual Report, University Health Services., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report, Mental Health Division of the Gannett Medical Clinic., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report, Office of the Treasurer., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report, College of Architecture, Art, and Planning., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report, New York State College of Home Economics., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report, College of Engineering., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Annual Report, Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Annual Report, Division of Biological Sciences., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Annual Report, Andrew Dickson White Professors at Large., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report, Society for the Humanities., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Annual Report, Six Year Ph.D. Program., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report of the Dean of the College of Arts and Sciences., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report, Vice Provost., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report, Office of Admissions., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Annual Report, Center for Research in Education., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Annual Report, Director of the University Libraries., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Annual Report, Division of Unclassified Students., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Annual Report, Division of Summer Session and Extramural Courses., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Annual Report, Director of the Budget., 1968-69 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Annual Report, Vice President Business Depts., 1968-1969 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Annual Report, Office of the Controller., 1968-1969 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Annual Report, Office of Regional Resources and Development., 1968-1969 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Annual Report, Cornell University Press., 1968-1969 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Tape Recordings
    - Commission of Williams Commission, April 1968; 3923-3928
    - Committee on Student Involvement in Decision 3935-3962 Making (Morison Commission), 3929-3933
    - James A. Perkins' Convocation Speech, September 21, 1966; 5456
    - James A. Perkins' Inauguration, October 4, 1963; 5457
    - James A. Perkins' Inauguration Luncheon, October 4, 1963; 5458
    - James A. Perkins1 Address to Ithaca Chamber of Commerce, March 1964; 5459
    - James A. Perkins and Dale R. Corson's Statements Concerning the Afro-American Institute and Related Events, 5460
    - James A. Perkins' Speech at Cornell Club of Buffalo Honoring Mr. And Mrs. Alfred M. Saperston, 1966; 5461
  - Transcripts
    - Commission of Williams Commission, April 1969; 3923-3928
  - Phono Disc
    - Inauguration of James A. Perkins, October 4, 1963; R-57
  - Broadsides
    - Cornell Greeting, in Latin, to the University of Vienna on the Occasion of its 600th Anniversary., 1965
    - Greetings from Cornell to Christian Albrecht University, Kiel Germany, on their 300th Anniversary., 1965